

Fahmi Nurcahya Software Engineer

🔘 Karawang, Indonesia.

(C) +6285718456591

PROFILE

3+ years of experience as a Software Engineer, I excel in designing, developing, and managing efficient and reliable software solutions.

I possess a profound understanding of modern programming languages, software architecture, and best practices in application development.

I have actively contributed to high-

I have actively contributed to highquality, complex software development projects that meet client needs.

Furthermore, I am committed to continuous learning and growth within the realm of technology.

SOCIAL

(7) fahminurcahya

₩ fahminurcahya

@ @fahminurcahya

EDUCATION

Bechelor of Informatic Engineering

> University Of Singaperbangsa Karawang

2015-2019

EXPERIENCE

MIDDLEWARE DEVELOPER

July 2021 - July 2023

PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia

- Created RestAPI service in ESB to integrate the requirements between BRI channels and third-party entities.
- Integrated applications with various formats such as JSON, ISO, and WSDL.
- Developed stored procedures in SQL Server.
- Acted as a dedicated middleware programmer for the BRI insurance platform (BRISURF).
- Designed the system's application flow, created API specification documentation, and conducted testing.
- Developed dashboard applications using React.js and Express.js.
- Conducted problem-solving and monitored services using Kibana.
- Implemented technologies such as Redis, Kafka, Elasticsearch, Bitbucket, and Bamboo.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

July 2020 - Juni 2021

PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT AZEC Indonesia Management Service

- Developed several dashboard applications using Golang, AngularJS, and Docker as containers for the applications.
- Enhanced new features on existing dashboards using Java.
- Created API services using Golang as the programming language on the server side, with PostgreSQL as the database.

BOOTCAMP JAVA DEVELOPER

December 2019 - Juni 2020

PT Xsis Mitra Utama

- Bootcamp as a java developer

SKILLS

Web Apps

HTML5 / CSS / Boostrap
Javascript / Typescript / ReactJs / AngularJS
Node Js / Express Js (ES5/ES6)
PHP (Laravel) / Golang / Java (Spring Boot)
RDBMS(MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL) / MongoDB / Redis

Mobile Apps

Dart / Flutter framework Kotlin / Java

Others

Git, Docker, Microservices, Product Software AG, Figma / Canva / Adobe Ilustrator, Firebase, Push Notofication, Adsanse Mobile

PORTOFOLIO & CERTIFICATES

Show Portofolio